<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
    <meta type="array">
        <description>CSH for rggooglemap</description>
        <type>CSH</type>
        <csh_table></csh_table>
        <fileId>EXT:rggooglemap/locallang_csh.xml</fileId>
    </meta>
    <data type="array">
			<languageKey index="default" type="array">
				<label index="show.alttitle">What to display</label>
				<label index="show.description">Select the views you need</label>

				<label index="key.alttitle">Google Maps Key</label>
				<label index="key.description">You need to have a Google Maps Key. Put it into the Extension Manager if you just need one. It is domain specific and you get it at http://code.google.com/apis/maps/signup.html</label>

				<label index="categoriesselected.alttitle">Available categories</label>
				<label index="categoriesselected.description">Select all categories which are available in the frontend.</label>

				<label index="categories.alttitle">Active categories</label>
				<label index="categories.description">All POIs whose category is selected are displayed on the map.</label>
				<label index="startingpoint.description">Define the pages on which the records are saved.</label>
				<label index="recursive.description">Define the depth of the page tree which is used to get the records.</label>

				<label index="width.description">Width &amp; Height of the map</label>
				<label index="lng.description">Longitude &amp; Latitude for the map after loading</label>
				<label index="zoom.alttitle">Zoom Level</label>
				<label index="zoom.description">1 is far far away, 13 is very near</label>

				<label index="type.alttitle">Map Types</label>
				<label index="type.description">Select the map types you want to display. &lt;br /&gt;Use Mapnik and T@H for alternative map types which are open source and which you can extend yourself. More information at http://www.openstreetmap.org</label>
				<label index="nav_controls.description">Let the user zoom in and out and navigate on the map</label>
				<label index="type_controls.description">Let the user switch map types.</label>

				<label index="useBoundsOnStart.description">If set, the map will display all available records by setting the correct position &amp; zoom level</label>
				<label index="loadDynamicList.description">Show a dynmic list of records which are currently displayed on the map.</label>

				<label index="showondefault.description">Enter the UID of the record you want to show on default. If you are using more than one table you need to add the tablename too like tt_news:123</label>


				<label index="defaultCountry.description">If the users come from just 1 country, use this field to hardcode the country for the geocoding. Otherwise create a select or input field in the template to let the users pick their countries.</label>
				<label index="radiusSearch.description">USe this option to let the user search in a specific area</label>


			</languageKey>
    </data>

</T3locallang>